cannabis.com 2019-04-02

# Updated 2018 Weedmaps Privacy Policy

## 1\. General Statements

Welcome to the Weedmaps family of sites and software! This Privacy Policy is a legally binding contract between Ghost Management Group, LLC or its applicable affiliate that owns or controls the applicable Website or provides the applicable Services that you may be accessing or using (“ **Weedmaps** ”, “us”, “we” or “our”), on the one hand, and you and your successors and heirs and (if applicable) the corporate entity you represent (“you” or “your”), on the other hand. This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information when you access or use Weedmaps’ (a) websites, portals, mobile applications, channels, and software, including weedmaps.com, marijuana.com, mmjmenu.com, cannabis.com, and safeaccessmd.com, and (b) social media pages and channels (collectively, the “ **Websites** ”), including any services, features, media, functions, content, tools, and links contained or offered therein (collectively, the “ **Services** ”). When you use the Websites or Services, you consent to our collection, use, modification, and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept and agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not access or use any of the Websites or Services or create an account or user profile.

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by (i) sending you an e-mail communication to the e-mail address you most recently provided to us, (ii) sending a push notification or in-app notification, (iii) prominently posting a notice of the changes on the Websites, or (iv) requiring you to check a box indicating your assent to the updated terms. Continued use of any of the Websites or Services following any applicable notice of such material changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. We may also post additional privacy policies or statements that apply to certain portions of the Websites or Services, and your access to and use of such Websites or Services shall be deemed to be your approval and consent to such additional privacy policies or statements.

## 2\. Information We Collect And How We Use It

### How Weedmaps Uses Your Information

We generally use your information to:

  1. Facilitate the creation of and to secure your User Account (as defined below) on the Services;
  2. Identify you as a user in our system;
  3. Provide, personalize, and improve the Services;
  4. Provide feedback and user base demographics to third-party businesses listed on the Websites or Services;
  5. Communicate with you about your use of the Services;
  6. Develop new products and Services,
  7. Track usage of the Websites and Services;
  8. Customize the advertising you view and recommend content;
  9. Backup our systems and allow for disaster recovery;
  10. Fulfill your requests and provide customer support;
  11. Send newsletters, surveys, offers and promotional materials related to the Services and your user preferences and behaviors and for other marketing purposes of Weedmaps using your contact information;
  12. Protect, investigate, prevent and potentially take action against possible fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activities;
  13. Respond to claims that Website content is inauthentic, counterfeit, or otherwise violates the rights of third parties;
  14. Respond to your requests for customer service;
  15. Protect our rights and the rights of other users;
  16. Enforce our Terms of Service, this Privacy Policy, and any other policies governing your access to or use of any of the Websites or Services; and
  17. As otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or in notices we provided to you.

We may also use your information to verify your geographic location. We may use your geographic location data to personalize and improve our Websites or Services, to recommend content, or determine whether the information you have requested is available in your location.

### How Weedmaps Discloses Your Information

  1. We may share your personal information with your consent or at your direction, including with third parties fulfilling orders or requests you place on our Websites.
  2. We may also share your information with others who perform services on our behalf.

  3. We also may disclose your information if we believe doing so is appropriate or necessary to prevent any liability, or fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses or to protect Weedmaps, our Websites, and Services; or any rights, property, or personal safety of Weedmaps or others.

  4. In the event that Weedmaps is or may be acquired by or merged with another company or involved in any other business deal (or negotiation of a business deal) involving sale or transfer of all or part of our business or assets, we may transfer or assign your information as part of or in connection with the transaction and such acquirer or merged entity may thereafter utilize your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Finally, in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, information may be transferred as a business asset.
  5. We may share your information with any of our affiliates.

We may also share aggregated and reasonably anonymized data with our partners, advertisers, and other third parties. You acknowledge and agree that the Websites can serve as portals to other businesses and consumers. Any requests, orders, or interactions you engage in with other businesses and consumers may necessitate the provision of information to such other party.

### Information We May Collect

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect. Among the information we collect, please note:

  1. Account Information: If you create an account on any of the Websites or Services (a “User Account”), we may store and use your full name, e-mail address, home address, phone number, zip code, and other information you may provide with your User Account, such as your gender and birth date. Your first name and last initial, as well as any photo you submit through the registration process, may be publicly displayed as part of your User Account profile. We may also store and use information regarding your means of age verification (e.g., drivers license) or medical marijuana recommendation, including your recommending doctor’s name and license number, contact information, verification methodology, and verification number. We may also store information on your order history and preferences with respect to orders placed from your account.
  2. Public Content: The information that you contribute through or post on the Websites or Services is intended for public consumption, including your reviews, tips, photos, videos, check-ins, comments, likes, posts, events, bookmarks, friends, lists, compliments, and basic User Account profile information. We may display this information through the Websites or Services, share it with businesses, and further distribute it to a wider audience through third-party sites and services.
  3. Communications: When you sign up for a User Account or use certain features, you are opting to receive messages from other Weedmaps users, businesses, and Weedmaps itself. While you can manage some of your e-mail preferences, please note that you cannot opt out of receiving certain administrative, transactional, or legal messages from Weedmaps. We may also track your actions in response to the messages you receive from Weedmaps or through the Websites or Services, such as whether you deleted, opened, or forwarded such messages. If you exchange messages with others through the Websites or Services, we may store them in order to process and deliver them, allow you to manage them, and we may review and disclose them in connection with investigations related to the operation and use of the Websites or Services. We may not deliver messages that we believe are objectionable, such as spam messages or requests to exchange reviews for compensation. If you send or receive messages through the Websites or Services via SMS text message, we may log phone numbers, phone carriers, and the date and time that the messages were processed. Carriers may charge recipients for texts that they receive. We may also store information that you provide through communications to us, including from phone calls, letters, e-mails, and other electronic messages, or in person. If you are a representative of a business listed on Weedmaps, we may contact you, including by phone or e-mail, using the contact information you provide us, make publicly available, or that we have on record for your business.
  4. Transactional Information: If you initiate a transaction through any of our Websites or Services, to the extent applicable (the “Transactable Sites”), we may collect and store information about you, such as your name, phone number, address, e-mail, and credit card information, as well as any other information you provide to us, in order to process your transaction, send communications about them to you, and populate forms for future transactions. This information may be shared with third parties for the same purposes. Weedmaps does not disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose of directly marketing their services to you unless you first agree to such disclosure that may advertise content directly to you on behalf of such parties. When you submit credit card numbers, we encrypt that information using industry standard technology. If you write reviews about businesses with which you transact through the Websites or Services, we may publicly display the fact that you transacted with those businesses.
    1. We collect non-personal information from you while you are browsing in the Websites. This information may include IP addresses to help analyze system administration, to gather broad demographic information, to enable ads to reach the right individuals, to report non-personal information to our advertisers, and to monitor the level of activity on Weedmaps. The information we collect from you visiting the Transactable Sites may include the URLs they came from, their IP addresses, the date and time of their visit or order, the number of visits and orders, the number of visits per browsing session, the server type, the operating system and browser type used to come to the site, the country, state, and telephone area code where their servers are located, the pages and page titles of our site that visitors viewed during their visit, whether the visitor’s computer is enabled for Java or cookies, browser language, applications and plug-ins, and any search terms entered on Weedmaps. We may also collect and store data that may be considered personal medical information, including regarding orders you prepare to place or actually place through any of the Transactable Sites.
    2. For individuals making purchases through the Transactable Sites, we may collect personal information that is reasonably necessary for third-party sellers to ship the products to you, verify your identity and eligibility to receive such products or services, and to communicate with you regarding purchases and any issues that may arise in connection with your purchase. This personal information includes your “ship to” information and your e-mail address. For product vendors and listing clients, we may collect information that is reasonably necessary for users to communicate with you regarding the purchases and shipment of goods and services purchased from you and any issues that may arise in connection with their purchase. This personal information includes the seller information provided during your listing or vendor registration and your e-mail address. When you make a purchase through the Transactable Sites, we may collect and maintain personal information from you, such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information, order number, referring URL, IP address, page you bought from, and a password. We collect this information, and other personal information as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, in order to facilitate the fulfillment of your order, to facilitate the communication with you about your order, and to send you promotional materials. Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contains, and these changes will be automatically kept for future use. We may require additional verifications or information from you before accepting any order.
  5. Activity: We may store information about your use of the Websites or Services, such as your search activity, the pages you view, the actions you take, the date and time of your visit, businesses you call or e-mail using our mobile applications, and purchases you make through the Transactable Sites. We also may store information that your computer or mobile device provides to us in connection with your use of the Websites, Services, or Transactable Sites, such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, browser language, IP address, mobile carrier, phone number, unique device identifier, advertising identifier, location (including geolocation, beacon based location, and GPS location), and requested and referring URLs. You may be able to disallow our use of certain location data through your device or browser settings, for example by disabling “Location Services” for the Weedmaps application in iOS privacy settings. We note that disabling Location Services may adversely impact the Website or Services experience and functionality and enabling such services may be necessary in some cases to allow certain transactions.

## 3\. Cookies

We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies, web beacons, tags, scripts, local shared objects such as HTML5 and Flash (sometimes called “flash cookies”), advertising identifiers (including mobile identifiers such as Apple’s IDFA or Google’s Advertising ID) and similar technology (“ **Cookies** ”) in connection with your use of the Websites or Services, third-party websites, Transactable Sites, and mobile applications. Cookies may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in e-mails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Websites or Services, such as your browser type, search preferences, IP address, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session.

Our uses for these technologies fall into one of the following general categories:

  1. Operationally Necessary: We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies that are required for the proper operation of our Websites, Services, and relevant applications, features, and tools. This includes technologies that allow you to access our Service, applications, and tools; that are required to identify irregular site behavior, prevent fraudulent activity, and improve security; or that allow you to use our other ancillary functions such as shopping carts, saved searches, or similar features.
  2. Performance-Related: We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies to assess the performance of our Websites, Services, and relevant applications, features, and tools, including, as part of our analytic practices, (i) to help us understand how our visitors use our Websites, (ii) to determine if you have interacted with our messaging, (iii) to determine whether you have viewed an item or link, (iv) to improve our Website content, applications, products, Services, or tools, and (v) to create new Website content, applications, products, Services, or tools.
  3. Functionality-Related: We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies that allow us to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing or using our Websites, applications, products, Services, features, and tools. This may include identifying you when you sign into our Websites or Services or keeping track of your specified preferences, interests, or past items viewed so that we may enhance the presentation of content on our Websites or Services or create new Website content, applications, products, Services, features, or tools.
  4. Advertising or Targeting-Related: We may use first-party or third-party cookies and web beacons to deliver content, including ads relevant to your interests, on our sites or on third-party sites. This involves using technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements and content that has been delivered to you, such as whether you have clicked on an advertisement.
  5. New Products and Services: We may use cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies to help develop new content, Websites, applications, products, Services, features, and tools. This may include keeping track of your preferences, interests, and behaviors and data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on.

This table helps describe the various reasons for our usages of cookies:

Purpose | Explanation  
---|---  
Processes | Intended to make the Websites, Services, and Transactable Sites work in the best way possible, ensuring that we exceed your expectations. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us whether you have signed up and created a user profile yet.  
Authentication, Security, and Compliance | Intended to prevent fraud, protect your data from unauthorized parties, and comply with legal requirements. For example, we use Cookies to determine if you are logged in to your User Account.  
Preferences | Intended to remember information about how you prefer the Websites or Services to behave and look. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us whether you have declined to allow us to use your phone’s geolocation data.  
Notifications | Intended to allow or prevent notices of information or options that we think could improve your use of the Websites or Services. For example, we use a Cookie that stops us from showing you the signup notification information if you have already seen it.  
Advertising | Intended to make advertising more relevant to users and more valuable to advertisers. For example, we may use Cookies to ensure you receive only interest-based ads, such as ads that are displayed to you based on your visits to other websites, or to tell us if you have recently clicked on a specific advertisement.  
Analytics | Intended to help us understand how visitors use the Websites, Services, and Transactable Sites, the effectiveness of certain advertisements, what kind of customer typically accesses the Websites or Services, and what specific promotions yield the best results. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us how our search suggestions correlate to your interactions with the search page.  
  
Managing Cookies: It may be possible to disable some (but not all) Cookies through your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect the functionality of the Websites, Services, and Transactable Sites. The method for disabling Cookies may vary by device and browser, but can usually be found in preferences or security settings. For flash cookies, you can manage your privacy settings by visiting the Adobe Macromedia site, located [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118).

## 4\. Third Parties

Third parties may receive information about you as follows:

  1. Advertisers: We may allow third parties to use Cookies through the Websites or Services to collect the same type of information for the same purposes that Weedmaps does for itself. In doing so, Weedmaps adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. Third parties may be able to associate the information they collect with other information they have about you from other sources. We do not necessarily have access to or control over the Cookies they use, but you may be able to opt out of some of their practices by visiting the following links: [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), [Omniture](http://www.adobe.com/marketing-cloud/web-analytics.html), and [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://aboutads.info/). Please note that opting out does not prevent the display of all advertisements to you. Additionally, we may share non-personally identifiable information from or about you with third parties, such as location data, advertising identifiers, or a cryptographic hash of a common User Account identifier (such as an e-mail address), to facilitate the display of targeted advertising. You may be able to limit our sharing of some of this information through your mobile device settings, as described in Section 2 above.
  2. Service Providers: We may rely on third-party providers to support or provide some of the features and options that are available through the Websites, Services, or Transactable Sites. We may also rely on third-party providers to perform certain services for us in connection with your use of the Websites or Services, such as communications and hosting services, network security, technical and customer support, tracking and reporting functions, quality assurance testing, payment processing, our own marketing of the Websites or Services, promotional and contest features, Transactable Sites’ product listings and brand management, and other functions. We may share information from or about you with these third-party providers so that they can perform their services or complete your requests. These third-party providers may share information with us that they obtain from or about you in connection with providing their services or completing your requests. Third-party providers may also share this information with their subsidiaries, joint ventures, affiliates, partners, or other companies under common control. Some of our web pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to you from our third-party providers, while preserving the look and feel of the Websites or Services. In such cases, please note that the information you provide is being provided to the third party.
  3. Aggregate Information: We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties, such as advertisers, brand managers, and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertisements, or certain products available in the Transactable Sites or the general characteristics of such users.
  4. Business Transfers: We may share information from or about you with our subsidiaries, affiliates, partners, joint ventures, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires Weedmaps or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess the same information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information, as described in this Privacy Policy.
  5. Businesses on Weedmaps: We may share information from or about you (such as your age and gender, your devices, and your use of the Websites, Services, and/or Transactable Sites (such as which businesses you bookmark or call)) with businesses listed on Weedmaps. You may adjust your settings to increase or decrease the amount of information we share. Keep in mind that businesses may see your Public Content (as defined in Section 2 above) and receive information about your transactions with them in the Transactable Sites, regardless of your settings. Additionally, if you make a phone call to a business through or in connection with your use of the Websites or Services, we may share basic information about your call with the business that you contacted, such as the date and time of your call and your phone number (and other information that would have been available to the business had you contacted them directly, and not through the Websites or Services). You may be able to limit our ability to collect and share your phone number through your phone’s settings or phone service provider.
  6. Investigations: We may investigate and disclose information from or about you if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure: (a) is reasonably necessary to comply with federal, state, or local legal process and legally binding law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us; (b) is helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Websites, Services, or Transactable Sites; or (c) protects our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users, affiliates, clients, partners, or the public, such as disclosures in connection with our Consumer Alerts program. If you flag or otherwise complain to Weedmaps about content available through the Websites, Services, or items on the Transactable Sites, we may share the substance of your complaint with the contributor of that content or product in order to provide an opportunity for the contributor to respond and/or remedy the situation.
  7. Links: The Websites or Services may contain links to unaffiliated third-party services. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with them and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on or applicable to all such third-party services. Some portions of the Websites and Services use the Google Maps API and this Privacy Policy therefore incorporates [Google’s Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) by reference.
  8. Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions: We may sometimes offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a “Promotion”) through the Websites or Services that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including allowing the sponsor of the Promotion to use your name, voice, and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, personal information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s official rules, such as on a winner’s list.

    * Please Note: If you agree to accept a Promotion from our third-party service providers or any third-party merchant, then you will receive e-mails separately from them and all information that you choose to disclose to them will be subject to their individual and separate privacy policies. If you later decide that you no longer want to receive their e-mails, then you will need to follow their own specific opt-out instructions. Following our directions for opting out of e-mail notifications and disclosure of personal information will not opt you out of third-party disclosures and related promotional communications.

## 5\. Changes To Your Profile And E-Mail Preferences

We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the personal information you provide to us. You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information that was provided as part of your registration with our Websites or Services. The Websites or Services may allow you to review, correct, or update personal information you have provided through the Websites or Services’ forms or otherwise. We will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then-active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that it is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information from our databases and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons. Also, any public postings or other communications you have made on the Websites or Services such as in forums or blogs cannot generally be removed. When you edit your personal information or change your preferences on the Websites or Services, information that you remove may persist internally for our own administrative purposes.

You may cancel or modify the e-mail marketing communications you receive from us by following the instructions contained within our promotional e-mails or in some cases by logging into your User Account and changing your communication preferences. This will not affect subsequent subscriptions, and if your opt-out preferences are limited to certain types of e-mails, the opt-out will be so limited. Subsequent or different subscriptions will remain unaffected. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your User Account or use of our Websites or Services, such as administrative and service announcements, and these transactional User Account messages may be unaffected even if you choose to opt out from receiving our marketing communications.

For those users utilizing the Transactable Sites’ online ordering feature, you can review, change, or delete the information you have submitted. You may ask to have information on your User Account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past purchases, you cannot delete information associated with past purchases. Also, as a security measure, we “back up” the data stored on our systems, ensuring that such prior information cannot be completely removed from our databases. As a result, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our backed-up or archived databases.

## 6\. Data Retention And User Account Termination

After you have confirmed the closing of your User Account we may retain information about you for the purposes authorized under this Privacy Policy unless prohibited by law. For example, we may retain information to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Websites, Services, or Transactable Sites or to comply with legal obligations. Please note that if a business is removed, and then reinstated at a later date, it will retain all of its previous reviews, ratings, and associated comments.

## 7\. Customer Data

As part of using the Services, users may submit electronic data or information they possess about their customers to the Websites and/or Services (“Customer Data”) for various purposes, including hosting and processing purposes in connection with the Services. Customer Data may include personal information, including, but not limited to, the name, location, and e-mail address of such customer. Any uses of the Customer Data by Weedmaps are conducted pursuant and subject to the terms of Weedmaps’ Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, or as required by law. If personal information pertaining to you as an individual has been submitted to us by a user of any of the Services as Customer Data and you wish to exercise any rights you may have to access, correct, amend, or delete such data, please inquire with the user (or his/her organization) directly. If an authorized user requests that we update or remove the Customer Data in question and the user has no ability to do so via use of the Services, we will acknowledge their request within 30 days. All inquiries relating to this Section 7 should be directed to us in accordance with Section 10 below.

## 8\. Children Using The Websites or Services

The Websites or Services are intended for adults only and require that users be no less than eighteen (18) years of age. Please note that certain of the Websites and Services require you to be at least twenty-one (21) years of age to access and use such Websites and Services. Please check the applicable terms and conditions for such Websites and Services for further information. Individuals under the age of eighteen (18) (or twenty-one (21) for applicable Websites and Services) are prohibited from creating a User Account and profile, accessing the Websites or Services, and/or purchasing products on the Transactable Sites. If you become aware that an underage user has created a User Account using false, stolen, or otherwise misleading information, please contact us immediately at 1-844-WEEDMAPS (933-3627), or at [customerservice@weedmaps.com](mailto:customerservice@weedmaps.com).

## 9\. Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. This includes using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which is software that encrypts the information you input. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

To most efficiently serve you when placing orders through our Transactable Sites site, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third-party banking managers, processing agents, and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order. Within the Transactable Sites, your information is kept on password-protected, limited access servers. Wherever possible and applicable, the Transactable Sites’ servers reside behind a corporate firewall that maintains controls on access to the system from both our internal network and the Internet.

If you believe that Weedmaps has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, you may contact us via e-mail at [privacy@weedmaps.com](mailto:privacy@weedmaps.com) or write to us at the following address:

Ghost Management Group, LLC Attn: Data Privacy Manager PO BOX 61267 Irvine, CA 92602 United States of America

## 11\. International Data Transfer

If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including, but not limited to, personal information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored, and used within the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your personal information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. By using the Websites or Services or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing, and storage of your information, including personal information, in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Please note that we take the privacy of our users seriously and therefore take steps to safeguard your personal information, including assuring an adequate level of data protection in accordance with international standards. If you would like additional information about your personal data and its use in connection with the Websites and Services, including revising any incorrect information, please contact the Data Privacy Manager at the address in Section 10 above. We will take such steps as we deem necessary to confirm your identity before sharing any personal data with you. We will attempt to respond to proper and confirmed requests relating to personal data within thirty (30) days, or as otherwise required by applicable law. If you are not satisfied with the way your request was handled, you may refer your request to your country’s data management authority. In the European Union, any such request should be directed to the Data Protection Authority in your EU Member State.

## 12\. California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights

California residents may request a list of certain third parties to which we have disclosed personally identifiable information about you for their own direct marketing purposes. You may make one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response. You may request this information in writing by contacting us at [privacy@weedmaps.com](mailto:privacy@weedmaps.com). Please allow up to thirty (30) days for a response.

## 13\. Do Not Track

Weedmaps does track its customers over time and across third-party websites to provide intelligent advertising, and does not respond to Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals. In addition, some third-party sites may keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, your web browser may allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked. Please review your web browser’s internet options for more details.
